[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original 747  was fitted with what kind of jet engines?", "correct_answer": "Pratt  Whitney JT9D-3", "incorrect_answers": ["General Electric CF6-80C2B1F", "Rolls Royce RB211-524G", "Kuznetsov NK-82 turbofans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Handel, Bach and  Scarlatti were all born in what year?", "correct_answer": "1685", "incorrect_answers": ["1789", "1785", "1613"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Italy?", "correct_answer": "Rome", "incorrect_answers": ["Venice", "Naples", "Milan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The moon is moving toward the Earth at a rate of 1.5 inches per year.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much did the first two Batmobiles from Batman Returns sell for?", "correct_answer": "$550,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$350,000", "$450,000", "$600,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Hollywood production Meet Joe Black had 5 wins and 2 nominations.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This vegetable is the main ingredient of the traditional French dish Cassoulet.", "correct_answer": "Beans", "incorrect_answers": ["Carrots", "Tomatoes", "Potatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The irrational mathematical constant, Pi has its own architectural monument in London, which was decorated with William Shanks version of the first 700 decimal places in 1937.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Green coffee beans can be roasted on the stovetop in a frying pan.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Order a Budweiser in Britain and you will get a beer from:", "correct_answer": "the Czech Republic or the USA", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "the Czech Republic", "the USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What disguise does Captain James West use to distract Loveless in a hilarious scene from the 1999 movie Wild Wild West?", "correct_answer": "A belly dancer", "incorrect_answers": ["An old lady", "A nurse", "A doctor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Absinthe Drinker and Woman Drinking Absinthe are paintings that immortalise the fame of absinthe. Who is the artist that painted them?", "correct_answer": "Picasso", "incorrect_answers": ["Van Gogh", "Monet", "Dali"]}]